你们好，漂亮的人们在上一个视频的末尾，我给了你们一些东西的预告
Hello you beautiful people at the end of the last video I gave you a little bit of a teaser about something
称为别名。
called aliases.
别名基本上是命令或构成命令的命令管道的小昵称
Aliases are basically little nicknames for your commands or for your command pipelines that make them
好记多了。
a lot easier to remember.
现在，在本视频中，您将学习如何创建自己的命令别名。
Now in this video you're going to be learning how to create your very own command aliases.
太令人兴奋了。
So very exciting.
现在，在这段视频中，我将一步一步地向您介绍。
Now in this video I'm going to walk you through step by step.
创建您自己的命令别名所需的一切。
Everything you need to do to create your own command aliases.
在视频结束时，您应该具备所需的所有技能，以便轻松创建
And by the end of the video you should have all the skills that you need in order to create easy to
记住管道的昵称，这样一旦你写好了它们，不管它们有多复杂
remember nicknames for your pipelines so that once you've written them no matter how complicated they
您是否可以一遍又一遍地使用它们，而不需要全部键入，而只需使用
are you can just use them over and over and over again without typing them all out just using instead
容易记住的昵称。
the easy to remember nicknames.
所以这是超级酷的东西。
So this is super cool stuff.
让我们继续前进，直接投入其中。
And let's go ahead and jump right into it.
好的。
OK.
因此，要开始创建您自己的命令别名，您需要做的第一件事是创建一个特殊的
So the first thing you need to do to start creating your own command aliases is to create a special
主文件夹中名为bash aliases的文件。
file called bash aliases in your home folder.
因此，要创建该文件，我们要做的是单击左上角的活动，然后
So to do that to create the file what we want to do is want to click on activities at the top left and
然后在这里的搜索栏中，只需键入单词text，它应该会出现这里显示的内容
then in the search bar here just type the word text and it should come up with the thing that says Here
文本编辑器。
text editor.
只需点击它，它就会打开一个新窗口，在那里我们实际上已经有了一个文件。
Just click on that and it will open up a new window where we've actually got a file.
这里顶部有一个按钮，您可以点击上面写着“保存”的按钮。
Now there's a button at the top here where you can click that says save.
所以我要单击保存，然后在我的主文件夹中键入一个文件，该文件开始于它所需的位置
So I'm going to click save and in my home folder I'm going to type a file that starts that it needs
完全按照我要告诉你的方式拼写。
to be spelled exactly the way that I'm going to tell you.
好的。
OK.
因此，首先您要键入句号或句号。
So first of all you type a period or full stop.
好的。
OK.
然后键入bash B。
Then you type bash B.
全部用小写字母表示。
SH all in lowercase.
然后是下划线，然后是别名，所以L R A S E S。
Then an underscore then aliases so a L R A S E S.
好的，这就是bash，在别名下划线，开头加句点或句号。
OK so that's bash underscore alias's with a period or full stop at the beginning.
所有内容均为小写，然后继续并点击保存。
Everything in lowercase and then go ahead and hit save.
好的。
OK.
现在我们有了bash别名的文件。
So now we have our bash alias's file.
实际上，我认为我们一刻也不需要航站楼，所以我也要关闭它。
And actually I don't think for a minute we'll need the terminals so I'm going to close that as well.
好的。
OK.
因此，请确保其拼写与显示完全相同。
So make sure it is spelt exactly as is appear.
句号，然后bash加下划线，别名为al-Ali，a，S.C.S，全部为小写。
Full stop then bash underscore aliases a Al-Ali a s.c.s everything in lowercase.
一旦你拿到了，我们应该都可以走了。
Once you've got the we should be all good to go.
所以现在您可能会想，为什么我们实际上需要在文件开头加上句号来命名该文件。
So now you might be wondering why did we actually need to name the file with a full stop at the beginning.
这很奇怪，我们通常不会这样命名文件，不是吗？
That's quite strange we don't normally name files like that do we.
句号使文件成为一种特殊类型的文件，称为隐藏文件。
Well that full stop makes the file a special type of file called a hidden file.
如果我们回到这里的文件浏览器，查看我们的主文件夹，您会看到bash
So if we go back into the file browser here and we look in our home folder you'll see that the bash
别名的文件实际上并不在那里。
alias's file isn't actually there.
它到哪里去了。
Where has it gone.
这是个隐藏文件。
Well it's a hidden file.
它有点隐蔽，但如果你点击这里的这个按钮，这里有三个栏，那么它的实际位置是什么
So it's kind of hidden but where it actually is if you click on this button here with the three bars
如果您单击该选项，然后单击此处，将会出现一个复选框，显示隐藏文件。
if you click that and then click on down here there'll be a checkbox that says show hidden files.
如果我们检查，我们将能够看到已经创建了abash别名Fall。
If we check that we'll be able to see that abash aliases fall has been created.
但实际上，这里还有很多我们以前从未见过的其他大量隐藏文件。
But there are actually also plenty of other plenty of other hidden files here that we haven't seen before.
但这里是我们的bash别名文件，我们当前正在编辑该文件，甚至还有一些
But here we are here's our bash alias's file that we're currently editing as well as actually even some
可能您甚至不知道的隐藏文件夹正在您的系统中潜伏。
hidden folders that maybe you didn't even know were sneaking around your system.
但不管怎样，我们不需要担心那些狂热分子，只要继续点击这三个栏就行了
But anyway we don't need to worry about those fanatics just go ahead and click those three bars again
并撤消查看隐藏文件，使其再次消失。
and undo viewing hidden files so it all disappears again.
所以你知道我们不必继续看床下的怪物了，现在我们可以继续
So you know we don't have to continue looking at monsters under our bed and now we can go ahead and
实际上，我们一直在编辑bash别名文件，一个案例，另一个案例，我们在bash别名文件中创建
actually keep editing the bash aliases file a case and another we're in bash aliases file making an
别名实际上非常简单。
alias is actually really quite easy.
下面是我们要为其创建别名的命令。
So here's the command that we want to make an alias for.
这将是一个非常长的命令，里面有很多复杂的东西。
It's going to be a really long command with loads of complicated stuff in it.
但是我们可以做到的。
But we can do this.
这不是什么新鲜事，只是相当复杂，相当长，所以我们可以把日期打出来。
It's not there's nothing new it's just quite complex it's quite long so we're going can type the date
指挥部。
command.
我们要把它传递给指挥部。
We're going to pass that into the command.
我们已经见过无数次了。
We've seen this a jillion times right.
我们假设分隔符是空格，我们将获得第一个字段。
We're going to take that the delimiter is a space and we're going to get the first field.
好的。
OK.
现在我们也想要一份这些数据的副本。
Now we were also wanted to have a copy of that data.
我们想要拍摄快照，这样我们就可以使用T命令并将其保存在主文件夹中名为的文件中
We want to take a snapshot so we can take the T command and save that in a file in our home folder called
完整日期。
full date.
前州立大学博士好的，到目前为止我们做得很好，那么我们就来拍一张这一天的快照
Dr. ex-state Okay so we're doing well so far then we're going to take a snapshot of just the day of
这周。
the week.
我们将把它保存在主文件夹中的一个名为“短期策略”的文件中。
We're going to save that in our home folder in a file called short date tactics.
然后输出的所有内容都将传递到echo命令，但也会给出回声
And then everything that comes out we're going to pass into the echo command but also give the echo
掌握自己的论据。
command its own argument.
这是一个相当长的评论。
That's quite a long comment.
正确的。
Right.
所以我们在这里做了很多事情。
So we're doing a lot of stuff in here.
但问题是它很长，因为您可以看到别名是多么有用。
But the point is that it's long because you can see how useful alias's are right.
因此，让它在您的计算机上运行的唯一方法就是不让Ziyad做得很好，除非在
So the only thing to make it work for your computer is instead of having Ziyad Well unless in the one
极有可能您的名字也是Ziyad，并且您选择它作为您的虚拟服务器上的用户名
in a jillion chance that your name is also Ziyad and you chose it to be your user name on your virtual
我认为不太可能的机器。
machine which I think is unlikely.
但是，如果您是半消息用户，而不是其他用户，请继续使用您的用户名进行更改，以便
But if you are semi message but otherwise just go ahead and change that with your username so that it
匹配您计算机上的正确路径，否则您将开始收到如我所说的错误
matches the correct path on your computer otherwise you're going to start getting errors like I said
如果你，如果你的用户名是你知道的，萨利，只要把它改成我就行了。
if you if your username was you know Saly just change it to me.
莎莉，好的，但是我的是齐亚德，所以我就不说了。
Sally OK but mine was Ziyad so I'll keep it at that.
好的。
OK.
这就是我们想要的命令。
So this is the command that we want.
我们给它取个别名吧。
Let's make an alias for it.
比方说，我们想要这样做，而不是每次想要时都键入这个庞大的命令
Let's say for example we wanted to instead of typing out this massive command every time we wanted to
去做吧，而不是简单地把它打出来。
do it instead of just typing it out.
如果我们只想输入GET DATES(获取日期)，而它将是Alias，该怎么办？
What if we wanted to just type get dates and that was going to be Alias.
我们所要做的就是键入单词alias，这是一个特殊的单词，然后按空格键，然后获取
What all we have to do is just type the word alias which is a special word then press a space then get
日期为等号，然后两边各有一个撇号，来吧，所以您可以看到有一个
dates an equal sign and then an apostrophe on either side of that come on so you can see there's an
这里有撇号。
apostrophe here.
这里有一个撇号。
And there's an apostrophe here.
好的。
OK.
就像整个庞大命令的两边各有一个引号，然后在开头加上别名。
So like a single quote on either side of the whole massive command then alias at the beginning.
别名的名称用等号加引号，然后在MASK命令的两侧用引号引起来。
The name of the alias an equal sign and then quotes on either side of the massive command.
所以我们要说的是，嘿，我想做一个别名叫Get Dates。
So what we're saying is hey I want to make an alias called get dates.
这完全等同于这个命令。
That is exactly equal to this command.
现在，当我们保存并关闭它时。
Now when we save it and close it.
所以我们需要关闭编辑器，然后单击这里的这三个栏。
So we need to close the the editor so we go with click on these three these three bars over here.
单击关闭确定，然后单击关闭。
Click Close OK and close.
我认为，所有这些都是大体上的，只是把它往下拖，然后关闭。
All of this in general I think and just drag that down and close.
当我们在一号航站楼打开的时候，我们重新启动了我们的终端，这个别名应该已经加载好了，所以我想让你
And when we open at terminal one we reboot our terminal that alias should be loaded OK so I want you
把这些别名看作是你自己的命令。
to think of these alias's as being like your own commands.
好的。
OK.
所以如果我们尝试运行get date命令，我们应该称之为。
So if we try and run the get dates commands shall we call it.
如果我们继续按Enter键，记住get date是我们的别名，实际上
And if we go ahead and press ENTER remembering that get dates was the name of our alias we actually
获取一些输出。
get some output.
所以这很酷。
So that's pretty cool.
现在，如果我们继续查看主文件夹中的，我们还会看到已经创建了两个新文件
Now if we go ahead and look in our in our home folder we'll also see that two new files have been created
转换为全日期点文本和短日期点文本。
to full date dot text and short date dot text.
那么让我们继续查看一下文本的日期。
So let's go ahead and take a look in for date that text.
我们实际上已经走了，拿到了完整的日期。
We've actually gone and got the full date.
所有数据都已传入，并确定DOT采取的日期。
All the data has been passed into that and sure date DOT takes.
他刚刚度过的一周中的某一天并不令人敬畏。
He has had just the day of the week passed in is not awesome.
好的。
OK.
因为这来自别名(如果我删除这些别名并继续运行以获取再次开始的日期)
Because this has come from the alias if I delete those and go ahead and run to get dates come on again
我们看到文件已经创建。
we see that the files have been created.
再来一次，里面有相同的数据。
One more time with the same data in them.
所以这太酷了，对吧。
So this is super cool right.
比方说，与其打出那么长的别名真的真的不会来
Like instead of typing out that really really really long Aliase really really don't come and every
现在我们想要获得该功能，因为我们已经创建了一个别名，并且基本上给出了一个可爱的昵称
time we wanted to get that functionality because we've created an alias and basically given a cute nickname
命令get date而不是庞大的管道，我们现在可以获得相同的功能，但是在
to the command get dates instead of the massive pipeline we can now get the same functionality but in
一种更容易记忆的方式，也是一种实际上很容易复制的方式。
a much easier to remember way and the way that's actually easy to reproduce.
所以这真的很棒。
So that's really awesome.
但现在让我给你看一些超级酷的东西。
But now let me show you something super cool.
好的。
OK.
实际上，您还可以在更大的管道中使用别名。
You can actually also use aliases in bigger pipelines.
因此，可以将您的别名看作是它自己的管道。
So think of your aliases just being its own pipeline right.
如果您别名(如果您保存的最小管道可以接受标准输入)中的第一个命令
If your alias if that mini pipeline that you save can accept standard input if the first command in
它可以接受标准输入，然后您可以通过管道连接到别名并运行整个管道，然后
it can accept standard input then you can just pipe to the alias and run the whole pipeline and then
摆脱别名，继续下去，就像有了自己的小管道建设挡路一样。
pipe out of the alias and continue on it's like having your own little pipeline building block.
所以让我带你去看看好的。
So let me show you OK.
假设我们希望我们的命令有一个别名，该别名显示一个月前的日历
Let's say that we wanted to have an alias for our command that showed a calendar with one month before
在当月之后的一个月，所以这个月的骗局就是奶牛。
and one month after the current month so that the con for that would be cow.
那么一就是一。
Then a one be one.
好的，那么在一个月之前的一个月之后，我们得到当前的月份，在我一个月之后得到一个月
OK so after one month before one month and we get the current month with one month after I'm one month
在此案之前，这是命令。
before the case that's the command.
如果我们返回到这里，请单击这三个水平箭头、水平条、抱歉并显示隐藏
If we go and head back in here click these three horizontal arrows horizontal bars sorry and show hidden
文件。
files.
单击我们的bash别名文件，打开并转到文件中的新行。
Click on our bash aliases files open up and go onto a new line in the file.
让我们为该命令创建一个新别名。
Let's create a new alias for that command.
好的，我们要说。
OK so we're going to say.
我们将把魔术简称为日历魔术。
We're going to call magic short for calendar magic.
我要输入一个等号，然后你就可以输入一些语音符号了。
I'm going to type an equal sign and then you can actually type some speech marks.
好的，你不必用单引号。
OK you don't have to have the single quotes.
你也可以有言语痕迹。
You can have speech marks as well.
我要把那头牛打出来。
I'm going to type that cow.
然后是选项。
Then the option.
给我吧。
Give it.
第一个是它自己的论点，然后是B。
Number one is its own argument then a B.
大写B，那么就有了自己的论点。
Capital B then one has its own argument.
我们将输出到我的主目录中一个名为Thing Dotty XTi的文件中，当然，请记住
And we're going to output into a file in my home directory called Thing Dotty XTi And of course remember
将此位替换为您在虚拟机上使用的用户名。
to replace this bit with your user name that you're using on your virtual machine.
好的，我们称之为魔术。
OK so we're going to call that magic.
但是这里的母牛指挥。
But the cow command here.
正确的。
Right.
COW命令只接受命令行参数，默认情况下不能通过管道传递给CALL命令。
The cow command only accepts command line arguments you can't piped to the call command by default.
所以要使它成为有效的管道，你可以访问整个Cal神奇的东西，一个有效的管道
So to make this a valid pipeline that you can access this this whole Cal magic thing a valid pipeline
你可以用管子送到那里。
that you can pipe to.
我们实际上需要将XOGS命令放在开头。
We need to actually put the X OGs command at the beginning.
好的。
OK.
所以我们就这么做吧。
So let's just do that.
如果你不知道我现在在做什么，请耐心等我，好吗？这是在做一座挡路大楼
If you don't know what I'm doing at the minute just bear with me OK which is making a building block
这整件事是我们可以用管道连接的。
this whole thing that we can pipe to.
好的。
OK.
所以这就是我们现在所做的，无论是什么，都将被输送到牛的魔术中，实际上
So that's what we've done right there now whatever is going to be piped to cow magic will actually be
通过管道传输到X Ogg的命令，然后将数据从标准输入转换为Cal不能转换的数据
piped to the X Ogg's command which will then convert the data from standard input which Cal doesn't
除了COW接受的命令行参数。
except to command line arguments which cow does accept.
因此，整个管道都会正常工作。
And so therefore the whole pipeline will work.
一定会很棒的。
It's going to be awesome.
相信我就好。
Just trust me.
好的。
OK.
让我们继续这样做，让我们关闭那个，保存并关闭关闭，关闭所有东西并关闭
Let's go ahead and do this let's close that save and close the close the close everything and close
我们的终端并重启它。
our terminal and reboot it.
新闻控制人员Alt和T谈论了九号航站楼。
The press control alt and t talked about terminal nine.
我呼应12 20：17进入考瓦尔魔术，接下来会发生的是，我将以命令的形式呼应这些数据
I echo 12 20:17 into Cowal magic what's going to happen is I'm going to be echoing this data as command
将参数行到MAGIC命令。
line arguments to the magic command.
所以我们预计会发生的是，我们预计我们会在2017年12月
So what we're expecting to happen is that we're expecting that we're going to get December 2017 the
日历上有前后各一个月的日历。
calendar for it with a month before and a month after.
好的。
OK.
保存到主目录中的文件。
Save to a file in our home directory.
所以如果我按Enter键，我们不会得到任何输出。
So if I press Enter we don't get any output.
但是如果我们进入这里的文件，我们会看到这里有一个文件，叫做Things That Take。
But if we go into our files here we will see that there is a file in here called things that takes take.
我们实际上已经设法保存了一个月前一个月和一个月前2017年12月的日历
We've actually managed to save the calendars for December so December 2017 one month before and one
一个月后，我们的家庭文件夹里出现了一种叫做“Take t”的东西。
month after into a fall called things that takes t in our home folder.
如果我真的得到了这些隐藏文件，那么发生这种情况的原因可能会容易得多。
And the reason that happened is probably a lot easier to see if I actually get one of these hidden files.
不，不。
No no.
我会的，我会留着它们，否则我会失去我现在的位置
I will I will keep them because otherwise I'll lose where I am.
但发生的情况是，我们重复了我们基本上传递给ex ogs命令的情况。
But what happened is we echoed we basically passed to the ex OGs command.
12点和20点17分的两条信息，然后作为命令行参数提供给日历
Two pieces of information at 12 and 20:17 which were then given as command line arguments to the calendar
指挥部。
command.
所以你可以看到所有这些东西是如何开始连接在一起的，我们已经制作了一条迷你管道，名为
So you can see how all this stuff is starting to tie together and we've made a mini pipeline called
Cowe Magic现在可以在我们想要的任何时候运行命令，所以我们不必键入以下内容
cowe magic that will now be able to run a command whenever we want so we don't have to type out this
丑陋的事情，我们只需要知道有多神奇，因为我们让第一个命令成为可能
ugly thing we just have to know how magic and because we made it possible to pipe to the first command
在我们的别名中，整个管道都会工作，我们可以在任何程序中像迷你建筑挡路一样使用它
in our alias the whole pipeline will work and we can use it like a mini building block in whatever programs
我们想做的东西。
that we want to make.
那么，这是多么令人敬畏的权利。
So how awesome is that right.
您能看到为管道编写别名并在中使用这些别名的能力有多么强大吗？
Can you see how crazily powerful the ability to write alias's for pipelines and use those aliases in
管道实际上可能是正确的。
the pipelines can actually be right.
你用这种能力所能达到的可能性真的是无穷无尽的。
The possibilities really are limitless with what you can achieve with that ability.
所以我们就把它留在这里吧。
So let's just leave it there.
我会让你的头脑因此而大吃一惊。
I'm going to leave your mind blown with that.
继续，现在总结一下我们所了解的关于别名的知识。
Go ahead and now take a summary of what we've learned about alias's.
好了，现在脑筋急转弯就到此为止了。
OK so that's enough of being mind blowing for now.
我希望你和我一样对你在这段视频中学到的东西感到兴奋，那就是锯齿混叠绝对是一种
I hope you're as excited as I am by what you've learned in this video that aliasing aliasing is an absolutely
令人难以置信的能力，如果使用得当，具有真正无限的潜力。
incredible ability with really limitless potential if used in the right way.
所以让我们快速回顾一下，以确保你们都记下来了。
So let's just have a quick recap to make sure that you've got it all down.
所以在这段视频中，首先你会了解到别名基本上就是一个容易记住的昵称
So in this video first of all you learn that an alias is basically just an easy to remember nickname
用于在管道中连接在一起的一个命令或一系列命令。
for a command or series of commands joined together in a pipeline.
现在，要创建别名，首先需要有一个名为点划线、下划线别名或小写的文件
Now to create an alias you need to first have a file called dot dash underscore aliases or in lowercase
在您的主文件夹中。
in your home folder.
这就是您实际放置数据文件的位置，您实际将别名和这些别名放在其中
And that's where you actually put your data file that you actually put your aliases in and these aliases
因此将特定于您的用户。
therefore will be specific to your user.
现在，作为一个加分点，您可以学习文件名开头的句号、句号或圆点
Now as a bonus point you learn a period or full stop or a dot at the start of a file name makes that
文件隐藏。
file hidden.
您还了解了如何在文件查看器中打开或关闭隐藏文件的可见性。
So and you also saw how to turn on or off the visibility of hidden files in your file viewer.
好的。
OK.
现在位于bash别名文件中。
Now inside the bash aliases file.
所以这实际上很容易做一个别名。
So that is actually quite easy to make an alias.
正确的。
Right.
这是您先输入关键字别名(全部小写)的方法。
This is the way that you do it first you type the key word alias all in lowercase.
然后放一个空格，然后放上别名。
Then you put a space and then you put the alias name.
所以当我们有了约会，或者它被称为魔术，或者随便你怎么称呼它，那就是你的昵称。
So as we get dates or it was call magic or whatever you want to call it that's your nickname.
好的。
OK.
然后在别名和等号之间加一个等号，而不添加空格
Then you put an equal sign without adding a space with space at all between the alias and the equal
你放进去的签名。
sign you put in.
所以你只要立即画一个等号就行了。
So you just put an equal sign immediately.
然后你打开一些报价。
Then you open some quotes.
这些引号可以是使用撇号的单引号，也可以是像您这样的普通双引号
These quotes can be either single quotes using an apostrophe or you know normal double quotes like you
将再次用于语音标记，没有任何空格，没有任何空隙。
would use for speech marks again without any spaces without any gaps.
在等号之间，您只需创建您的管道或使用您的命令。
Between the equal sign then you just create your pipeline or you use your command.
同样，你可以像往常一样选择和指挥一夫一妻制。
Again you can have options and command monogamists just like you normally would.
好的，你想吃多久就吃多久。
OK these can go on for as long as you want.
好的。
OK.
现在，只要确保重新启动终端，您就可以永远访问该别名。
Now as long as you make sure that you restart your terminal you'll then have access to that alias forever.
好的。
OK.
而作为另一个加分点看你看，你得到的两个加分点在总结中应该是应该的
And as another bonus point looking you look you get two bonus points in the summary should be should
感到被宠坏了。
be feel very spoiled.
但是，只要您确保该管道中别名中的第一个命令实际上可以通过管道传输
But as long as you make sure the first command in that alias in that pipeline can actually be piped
要确定，您只需通过管道将别名教皇连接到昵称，您就可以像通过管道连接到
to OK then you can just pipe to the alias pope to the nickname and you'll it as if you're piping to
整条管道。
the whole pipeline.
如果我再说一次烟斗这个词，我可能会发疯的。
If I say the word pipe one more time I'm probably going to go insane.
但是你说对了。
But you get the point right.
如果使您的管道可以通过使用X OGS命令或仅使用
If you make it so that your pipeline can be piped to either by using the X OGs command or by just using
一个可以接受标准输入的普通命令，那么您基本上可以使用
a normal command that can accept standard input then instead of having to you can basically use the
将许多管道别名为正在建设某一大型其他管道中的一座小建筑挡路
alias that many pipeline as a tiny building block in some massive other pipeline that you're building
创造出真正史诗般的功能。
to create a really epic bit of functionality.
好的，根据您所学到的管道、X参数和所有类型的内容，以正确的方式使用别名
OK so alias is used in the right way with what you've learnt about piping and X args and all sorts of
制造这些长管道的材料是一种史诗般的能力。
stuff making these long pipelines is an epic epic ability.
因此，现在您可以构建自己的命令管道，甚至可以保存它们以备以后理解时使用
So now you can build your own command pipelines and even save them for use later when you understand
基本上Linux操作系统中的任何东西都可以使用命令行进行修改。
that basically anything in the Linux operating system can be modified using command line.
你真的是让Linux操作系统如此令人惊叹的皇冠上的明珠，因为任何东西都可以
You really are the crown jewel that makes the Linux operating system so amazing because anything can
使用命令行进行编辑。
be edited using the command line.
您知道，必须创建这些命令来说明如何使用这些命令，并将它们通过管道连接在一起来完成
And you know had to create these come on how to use these commands and piped them all together to do
你想要什么都行。
whatever you want.
您真的拥有一个万能钥匙，可以将您的计算提升到一个新的水平。
You've really got a master key that take your computing to the next level.
但是要利用这一点，你现在所需要的只是简单的积木，实际上
But in order to take advantage of this all you need now are just simple building blocks to actually
使用建造管道。
build pipelines with.
正确的。
Right.
所以在课程的下一节中，我们实际上将介绍一大堆这样的建筑
So in the next section of the course we're actually going to be covering a whole bunch of those building
块，因为本课程的下一节将全部介绍导航文件系统创建操作
blocks because the next section of the Course is all about navigating your file system creating manipulating
文件、创建文件夹、复制和粘贴文件、创建系统备份等等。
files making folders copying and pasting files creating backups of your system and so much more.
但在我们谈到这一切之前，我想确保你了解我们所拥有的一切
But before we get into all that goodness I want to make sure that you understand everything that we've
先在课程的这一节讲到，因为这是一个令人难以置信的基础性的、令人难以置信的
covered in this entire section of the course first because it's been an incredibly foundational incredibly
课程的重要部分。
important section of the course.
如果你理解了这一节的所有内容，你学到的其他东西都不会错太多。
If you understand everything in this section you will not go far wrong with anything else you learn
在使用Linux时。
when using Linux.
我也想确保你对你到目前为止取得的惊人进步表示衷心的祝贺。
And I also want to make sure your Jewely congratulated for your amazing progress so far.
你真的应该对你在这一节中所做的和你所学到的东西有一些认可
You really really deserve to have some recognition of what you've done in this section what you've learned
你已经走了多远。
at how far you've come.
在下一个视频中，我们将庆祝你们取得的令人印象深刻的进步
So in the next video we're going to have a celebration of your really impressive progress and a quick
回顾一下我们在这一节所讲的内容。
recap of what we've covered in the section.
一定会很棒的。
It's going to be awesome.
所以，回顾一下这一部分，以及一些当之无愧的庆祝和赞扬。
So review the section and some well-deserved celebration and praises.
我将在下一个视频中见到你。
I will see you in the next video.